New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Arbitration and Board of Grievances Meeting Minutes on Microfilm 6154 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Arbitration and Board of Grievances Meeting Minutes on Microfilm
1913-1922
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Arbitration
New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Grievances
6154 mf
0.56 cubic feet
5 microfilm reels
Minutes, microfilm.
5821368
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 06, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Arbitration; New York City Coat and Suit Industry Board of Grievances
5821368
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1913 (Reel 1)
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1913; 1 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  September-October 1913
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration and Board of Grievances, 1913-1915 (Reel 2)
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1913; 1 (Reel 2)
  October 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1914; 2 (Reel 2)
  January 1914.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1915; 3 (Reel 2)
  January 1915.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1915; 4 (Reel 2)
  April 1915.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913; 5 (Reel 2)
  May 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913; 6 (Reel 2)
  September 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913; 7 (Reel 2)
  December 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1915; 8 (Reel 2)
  February 1915.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1915; 9 (Reel 2)
  March 1915.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913 (Reel 3)
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913; 1 (Reel 3)
  July 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1913; 2 (Reel 3)
  August 1913.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration and Board of Grievances, 1914-1915 (Reel 4)
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1914; 1 (Reel 4)
  November 25, 1914.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1914; 2 (Reel 4)
  December 1914.
- Meetings of the Board of Arbitration, 1915; 3 (Reel 4)
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances and ILGWU Conference Committee, 1922 (Reel 5)
- Meetings of the Board of Grievances, 1915; 1 (Reel 5)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Conference Committee, 1922; 2 (Reel 5)
  Conference, May 1922